Cheryl Sacks

crsacks@gmail.com |413.281.1890

Profile

Knowledgeable, conscientious, and dedicated professional highly motivated to apply strong technical, communication and interpersonal skills in a challenging position. Experienced in Windows, Mac and Unix environments, Microsoft Office applications, Google Suite, Programming, WordPress, SQL, digital photography.

Professional Experience

IT Support Specialist/Analyst, Crane Stationery, North Adams, MA

2016-2021

- Analyzed business requirements for Product Design, Purchasing, Finance and Maintenance departments leading to successful development of Infor M3 documents as well as three corporate Workflow applications.
- Managed shopfloor data collection replacement project resulting in improved manufacturing efficiency and lower costs. Sourced barcode and tablet hardware. Developed and delivered employee training.
- Resolved software and hardware issue for employees and customers.
- Purchased and maintained hardware including computers and barcode equipment inventory.

Technology Specialist for Education, Pittsfield Public Schools, Pittsfield, MA

2014-2015

- Developed and delivered training workshops on computer skills, website development and Google Apps.
- Supported and trained teachers and students on effective use of instructional technology in the classroom throughout twelve school district. Wrote weekly "Tech Tips" for teachers. Applauded by principals and teachers for providing effective and empathetic support to teachers and students.

Video Producer/Office Manager, Dalton Community Television, Dalton, MA

2012-2014, 2015-2016

- Trained community producers on how to use video cameras and editing equipment.
- Produced, videotaped, and edited community television shows.

Project Manager, Photography Assistant, Robert Kaufman Commercial Photography, Newton, MA 1996-98

Mac environment - Designed product packaging, digital photo editing, created stock photography website.

Additional Professional Experience: Interleaf, Waltham, MA and Prime Computer Natick, MA

- Authored courseware and conducted technical training on proprietary software applications.
- Wrote technical white papers describing software functionality and features in layman's terms.
- Programmed "C" applications for shopfloor and manufacturing environments.
- Designed and implemented a "QuickStart" multimedia tutorial for electronic publishing software running on seven different hardware platforms.

Other

Award Winning Fine Art Photographer

1991-present

- Consult on photographic technique and digital photo editing and organizing.
- Exhibited locally and internationally. Signed prints purchased by hundreds of admirers.
- Selected to be in Art in the Embassies program. Multiple images chosen by Egyptian & Lithuanian Ambassadors.

Education

M.S. Computer Information Systems, Boston College, Carroll School of Management | Chestnut Hill, MA B.S. Computer Science, University of Michigan | Ann Arbor, Michigan